A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1975-1988
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1975-1988
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/3.901
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1 October 1990.
Organization
Series I: Athletics Boxes 1-7
Series II: Entertainment Boxes 7-10
Series III: Fall Convocation Boxes 11-12
Series IV: Finals, Founder's Day Boxes 13-20
Contents List
- Series I: Athletics
  - Basketball (2 folders) 1986-1988 (Box 1)
    - Basketball, Schedule, Correspondence 1985-1986 (Box 1)
    - Games Completed, President's Box, Guest Lists 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Basketball 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Basketball and the President's Box 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - Basketball and the President's Box (4 folders) 1979-1983 (Box 2)
  - Football (1 of 2) 1987 (Box 2)
  - Football (2 of 2) 1987 (Box 3)
  - Football (3 folders) 1986 (Box 3)
  - Football (4 folders) 1985 (Box 4)
  - Football (4 folders) 1983-1984 (Box 5)
  - Football (1 of 4) 1982 (Box 5)
  - Football (2-4 of 4) 1982 (Box 6)
  - Football (2 folders) 1981 (Box 6)
  - Football and the President's Box (4 folders) 1979-1981 (Box 7)
- Series II: Entertainment
  - Entertainment (1-2 of 4) 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Entertainment (3-4 of 4) 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Entertainment (1-2 of 4) 1986-1987 (Box 8)
  - Entertainment (3-4 of 4) 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - Entertainment (3 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Entertainment--Carr's Hill (Official) 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - --Events, Special, Other (4 folders) 1969-1984 (Box 10)
- Series III: Fall Convocation
  - Fall Convocation (6 folders) 1983-1987 (Box 11)
  - Fall Convocation (4 folders) 1979-1982 (Box 12)
- Series IV: Final Exercises, Founder's Day
  - Finals (3 folders) 1988 (Box 13)
  - Finals (1-2 of 3) 1987 (Box 13)
  - Finals (3 of 3) 1987 (Box 14)
  - Finals (3 folders) 1986 (Box 14)
  - Finals (1 of 3) 1985 (Box 14)
  - Finals (2-3 of 3) 1985 (Box 15)
  - Finals (3 folders) 1984 (Box 15)
  - Finals (3 folders) 1983 (Box 16)
  - Finals (1-2 of 4) 1982 (Box 16)
  - Finals (3-4 of 4) 1982 (Box 17)
  - Finals (1-3 of 4) 1981 (Box 17)
  - Finals (4 of 4) 1981 (Box 18)
  - Finals (4 folders) 1980 (Box 18)
  - Finals--Summer Session 1975-1977 (Box 19)
  - Founder's Day (5 folders) 1984-1987 (Box 19)
  - Founder's Day (4 folders) 1980-1983 (Box 20)
  - New Faculty Orientation 1982-1984 (Box 20)